The SCOAN Sunday Service.
You may be seated. Thank you.
Today we shall talk about: The Greatest Achievement On Earth
People believe until they become very very rich, famous, just talk about those things you desire for.
Ask yourself
What is the greatest achievement on Earth?
Ask your neighbor
What is the greatest achievement on Earth? (I can't hear you)
What is the greatest achievement on Earth?
Can somebody answer this question?
That : What is the greatest achievement?
The greatest achievement on earth is having Jesus Christ.
Having Jesus Christ
You listen to that. You achieved that?
Yes Man of God.
Oh, you listen to that.
She has got it wrong. Somebody who has Jesus and can not talk to Jesus,
and Jesus can not talk to her. Which kind of Jesus is that? Is he the dead one?
The only Jesus we know is Jesus of Nazareth, in the power of Holy Ghost.
If you have Jesus; you will be able to talk to Him and Himself will be able to talk to you
Prayer is a two way conversation; you talk and He talks. That is it.
But a situation where you are the only talking. To who?
Which Jesus? That is why I said; you got it wrong.
The greatest achievement on earth is to walk on the Spirit.
Are walking in the Spirit?
Yes
Hmmm. Ok what does Jesus say about me? Don't lie because I know what Jesus say about me.
What does he say now?
Now? Concerning me. Concerning you; you are a genuine Man Of God.
What will I say now? That is not the question I am asking you.
I think the greatest achievement on earth is to be filled with the Holy Spirit
and have Jesus Christ as the Lord and Savior and every other thing will be added unto you.
Are you filled?
Somehow.
Somehow. And what is not done well (is not done at all)
I say; what is not done well - somehow, it's not done at all. That is Jesus standard for you.
Ok thank you.
We are asking ourselves; The greatest achievement on earth.
because whatever you claim you have achieved, you are still struggling with peace.
You are still struggling with joy. Joy today, another one tomorrow
Your joy is not constant, your peace is not constant. Aaa I mean..
What is the greates achievement? Viewers, thank you for your time.
And I know the Lord will bless your time today.
Let's take the book of Romans 12. A Living Sacrifice,
"Therefore, I urge you, brothers and sisters, in view of God's mercy,
to offer your bodies as a living sacrifice, holy and pleasing to (who?) - God. To who?To God.
-this is your true and proper worship. Listen to that. this is your true and (what?) proper worship.
Do not conform to the pattern of this world, but be transformed by the renewing of your mind.
Then you will be able to do(what?)test and approve what God's will is - his good, pleasing and(what?)perfect will.
18 which is Roman 12, you take your reading from verse 1 to the end.
And the Book of Daniel 6:10 and 1 Corinthians 14:14 to 15 or to the end.
You have it good for you. And the Book of Acts 2:4 and the brother Job Chapter 11: 13 to 19
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Halleluyah!
As we continue, the book of Galatians 4:6 also will help. As we continue we will have more books to talk about.
As for me and my household;
The greatest achievement on earth is pray as God wants us to pray.
Prayer is the key, prayer is the key. Prayer is the Master Key
Jesus started with prayer and ended with prayer.
Prayer is the Master key.
Why should anyone not want a Master key? Master key to loose and to bind.
To pray as God wants you to pray as God wants you to pray is the greatest achievement on earth.
You will be able to know God's opinion about yourself and God's opinion about others.
You will be able to get involved in God's project, in God's Master plan.
There is God's project everywhere. God's projects, help is God's project
as God will have.... talk..as God will have pray as God will.. teach us God will...
These are God's projects. Such a life of prayer costs,
Such a life of prayer (what?) costs.
You know what I mean by costs? It demands sacrifice.
All Prayer Saints have spend hours everyday in prayer. All prayer Saints, God's people
have spend hours everyday in prayer.
This means ; prayer is a lifestyle to them.
Is prayer a lifestyle to you? A lifestyle to you? No.
Prayer can not be a lifestyle because:
With word of prayer on your lips, it is not possible for you to pray without ceasing.
Lifestyle means, praying without ceasing. Are you praying now? Are you in the attitude of prayer?
No, you are looking at me at the same time your heart is seized.
You can not do that. This is the level we want to build to.
The Saints were able to pray without ceasing because they were in the Spirit of prayer.
But you are not in the Spirit of prayer but prayer with word on your lips, not in your heart.
They were are able to achieve this because they were in the Spirit of prayer.
There is a difference between saying word and praying prayer.
What is prayer?
Prayer is a relationship that exists between God and his children.
A relationship that what? That what? That exists between who? (God) and his children
between God and Christians. Between God and believers. Between God and God's people.
Between God and God's person. A relationship that exists. What kind of relationship do you have?
And you are praying.
You must have a relationship before prayer
Who is God? God is Spirit. You; the real thing about you is Spirit too
So it means spirit, spirit. Spirit join himself, immerse, acts.
Your spirit means, heart. When I say 'heart', I mean your spirit.
Your real self not your body; it's spirit.
God is spirit. Now join himself, immersed
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbour
The real thing about you is spirit. Your real thing.
If God wants to talk to you, your heart is the contact point not your body.
So when you hear people say I hear God talking to you in the ear, you know its not God - heart
Heart means your spirit.
Your heart is the contact point , is the communication point.
Like the Book of Romans 9:1 said
His Spirit in our heart, in our spirit, enables us to cry naturally, that is, effortlessly
It is not the kind of prayer you pray now, when you are praying, you get tired. No, naturally the Spirit;
God's Spirit in our heart enables us to do what? To preach naturally, to cry naturally. "Abba ! Father!"
That Book of Galatians 4:6, Are you with me?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What am I saying if you are with me?
Am I just talking to myself? I am talking to myself.
I am going back.
God's Spirit in our heart it means;
For God's Spirit to come into our heart, our heart must act upon the Word of God.
Our heart must act upon what?( Word of God) Upon the Word of God.
His Spirit in our heart, enables us to cry naturally," Abba! Father!
Heart - what is heart?
Our life reflects what is in our heart,
Tell your neighbour
My life reflects what is in my heart.
When you do like this.... it means there is there is kind of joy in your heart.
(Crying) heart is troubled.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I am what is in my heart; you are what is in your heart,
Tell your neighbor
I am what is in my heart; you are what is in your heart,(I cant hear you)
I am what is in my heart; you are what is in your heart,
That is why we say; don't just get married to people because she is beautiful he is handsome.
Is good looking, famous but;
Love is a thing of the heart.
I am what is in my heart; you are what is in your heart.
My life reflects what is in my heart.
You talk about heart, heart , heart
The heart refers to the inner man, the man himself
That is heart - the man himself. Heart.
The heart - the man himself.
It is the seat of desire, the seat of will, emotion, knowledge, wisdom moral character.
It is the fountain of all he does - man, man
the man himself; the heart.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Inner my heart
Lord I want to be like Jesus; Inner my heart.
That is why God is interested in the state of your heart
He is interested in the state of our heart.
The heart - the man himself.
Let someone say - the heart the man himself (I can't hear you)
You see people waiting for healing, people are waiting for healing, you see them there.
If you truly believe in your heart, your character will reflect your faith.
You see somebody who has problem will start laughing, he knows he will be healed that is why he is laughing.
While you see some of them there(crying) Man of God help me. Aaaa you are here already.
Tell your neighbour
If you truly believe in your heart, your behaviour will reflect your faith.
Maybe some people are trying to change now. Ah Man of God is talking, let me start laughing.
No, that can not work.
Yaa you see some, will start saying " oh my God. Thank you Lord." Even before some are here today,
they have arranged party at home. They have arranged some food, friends
please I am coming back, please I want you to rejoice with me.
yet he still having that pain. Why?
If you truly believe in your heart, your behaviour will reflect your(what?) your faith.
He has arranged a party and in deed he will do that party today.(Amen)
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If you truly believe in your heart, your behaviour will reflect your faith.
That is why he say this capsule I don't know whether I should stop using it
I will ask Man of God after prayer
If you truly believe in your heart, tell your neighbour
If you truly believe in your heart, your behaviour will reflect your faith.
After the prayer I will tell Man of God whether I can still use this tablet.
After the prayer, I will tell Man of God whether I should go for medical check up.
to see whether I am healed. Tell your neighbour;
If you truly believe in your heart, your behaviour will reflect your faith.
Can you see what we call heart.
Heart - the man himself.
Heart - the seat of the will, wisdom, heart the seat of wisdom, knowledge the conscience.
His Spirit in our heart - God's Spirit in our heart enables us to cry naturally.''Abba! Father!"
A believing heart produces good work and right behaviour as proof of faith.
When you see somebody who is behaving ...... aah you know this one is not a Christian.
Please don't talk to me like that; I will deal with you
A believing heart produces right behaviour and good work as proof of faith.
Good work and right behaviour that honour Jesus,
reveal that true falith is already lodged in our heart.
Right behaviour and good jobs that honour God
reveal that true faith is already (what?) lodged in our hearts.
Take note: Right behaviour and good jobs never produce faith; they are the result of the faith.
That is why you can see me here. How much education?
You that is well educated and professional; Will you stand and be talking like this?
But because the spirit in my heart, enable me to talk naturally without carrying laptop,
without carrying book without carrying anything.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Without carrying anything, without having paper, without going back to the altar and
praise the Lord. Amen! You see, you see, Jesus is great. I am telling you, Jesus Jesus, Amen!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You talk naturally. Ability to talk.
This sense of fatherhood produces a natural basis for prayer.
So where are we going?
Now you have known your position; you are not what you say you are.
When it comes to things of the spirit. I don't want the last day to come before you know this.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
To be pure in heart, our heart must act upon the Word of God.
Tell your neighbour;To be pure in heart, our heart must act upon the Word of God.
I can't hear you.To be pure in heart, our heart must act upon the Word of God.
Our heart must act upon the Word of God to be pure in heart
How?
That is the question now. How?
By meditating on what we read in the Scripture and turning it over and over again in our heart.
So that our heart can act upon the Word, to influence our conduct
Aa, please don't talk to me like that. When the Word of God influences your behaviour
you will find yourself naturally not talking like that.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Not struggle to talk. Not struggle aa I don't want to talk like that; I don't know...oh my God.
When you finish talking aa you want to talk, you are struggling to stop your behaviour.
You keep trying to ...I don't want to do this; I find yourself doing them.
The heart has not yet act .
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We have to work and work and work to turn our hearts
In tune with God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Because our right behaviour is determined by the condition of our heart.
What is determined? Hee?
Our behaviour is determined by the what? by the condition of the of our heart.
Your behaviour is determined when the anger comes; What is this T.B.Joshua saying, I'm going home.
Nobody can stop you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbour
Our behaviour is determined by the condition of our heart.
Prayer is two is a two way conversation.
I talk to God and God talks to me - that is prayer.
I talk to God and God talks to me.
This is what I mean by:
God's Spirit in our heart enables us to cry, naturally, effortlessly, "Abba! Father!"
I talk to God and God talks to me.
Don't forget - God is Spirit. Those who want to talk to Him must do so in Spirit and Truth.
If you do not talk to Him in Spirit, it is not in truth.
If you do not talk to God in Spirit, it means it is not in truth and so it is all nothing - in vain.
In the name of Jesus, in the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus., in the name of Jesus. in the blood of Jesus.
If you do not talk to Him in the Spirit - because God is Spirit.
it is not in truth and so it is all nothing, all in vain.
It means you talk to the air; it means you are inviting satan to come and attack you.
But when satan hear the name of Jesus - oh who is talking there; this is what happened
to seven sons of Sceva. They were not talking to God in spirit.
So when they said Jesus, Jesus! Satan said - who is talking , who is talking there?
He wants to know who is talking talking. Who is talking?
By the time they trace you; you are the one talking,
They want to know by what authority,.Are you talking in spirit?
If they release you are not talking in spirit ; oh my God
Those nightmares, those attacks; you know sometimes when you pray and sleep;
that is when they will attack you. If I am talking to you.
Imagine when you now finish your fasting, for two days , three days fasting, you suffer so much.
You refuse to eat, you struggle not to eat not in command of God.
But command of your what? Yourself. After you try it, you try, it try it, you are about to die
You say no, I will not die, this fasting I must finish it today.
You now finally finish the fast; you say, thank God.
Jesus, I know you have accepted me.
By the time you now sleep; they will naked you and start giving you food.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Heart. Lets someone say heart.(Heart)
God listens to us when we pray and He replies in relation to the state of our heart .
He replies according to the state of our heart.
Let someone say - heart(heart) Let someone say - heart(heart)
My life reflects what is in my heart.
Are with me?
He replies in relation to the state of your heart.
He replies according to the what? the state of your heart.
The heart refers to the man himself
It is the seat of will, conscience, wisdom. It is the fountain of all you do.
Let someone say - the man himself; the heart. I can't hear you.
The man himself - the heart.
Tell you neighbour, take care of your heart. I can't hear you. Take care of your heart
Take care of your heart
Constantly pray in your heart without ceasing.
In hymns, in spiritual songs, making melodies in your heart to the Lord.
The best way to take care of your heart is to constantly pray in your heart,
in hymns, in spiritual songs.
I will praise Him - in your heart
I will praise Him forever more
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Constantly pray in your heart because saying words is not praying prayer.
You are saying words not prayer.
Tell your neighbour - say
You are saying words not prayer
I don't want you to waste your time, continue to say words and say you are praying when
Prayer is a two - way conversation.
You talk to God and God talks to you - that is prayer.
Please work on your heart.
To be pure in heart, your heart my heart must act upon the Word of God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
By meditating, and meditating, work. By meditating, meditating.
And one of the processing is to continue praying in your heart.
"In the name of Jesus, in blood of Jesus. Take more of me give me more of you.
Get your heart in order - it is the seat of God; it is the communication point.
It is the contact point - your heart.
The real thing about you is your heart
That is the real thing about you.
That is the landing point
That is the station - your heart
The Prayer you see me offer any moment from now is not that prayer that answer
the prayer that answer are the one that I have loaded myself. I am pregnant now
THE GREATEST ACHIEVEMENT ON EARTH
So You have to be pregnant of the Word to deliver.
You cannot continue praying all the time with the word of prayer on your lips
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Will you continue to say, In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus?
Any time you say that without the Spirit of God; your body is just
If people call you - how are you; you will not answer
because its not possible for you to answer because you are the one praying.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You are the one praying; In the name of Jesus - and someone say how are you, you will not answer
because you are praying and you are not the one praying.
It is the Spirit of Father in our heart that enable us to(what?) to pray. Oh my God
THE GREATEST ACHIEVEMENT ON EARTH
My brother come here, come. Let us demonstrate this to them.
You see my brother here. So now I want to pray, but I am not supposed to pray.
It is the Spirit of Father that is supposed to enable me to pray.
But now I want to pray just the same way you pray.
When I'm praying now, you call me. You talk to me,continue talking to me
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus
You don't know I am praying?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Talk louder, let people hear you.
In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus. (Hallo Sir) You are disturbing me , please I am praying.
That is the prayer we offer. We pray on our own and we are the one praying.
But with the help of Holy Spirit now, I want to pray. You call me hey. You talk louder let
people hear what you are saying.
Ok. (hallo Sir).How are you? How are you?
You see we are talking together and I am praying.
So how are you? Where are you going? (I am going to my seat). You are going to your seat. Ok
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Ok , ok look at the crowd, they are looking at us. What do you think is happening?
And I am praying and at the same time doing what?(Talking)
I'm praying at the same time talking. (They are trying to know what we are doing.
They are trying to know what we are doing; ok. They are still laughing. I don't know why they are laughing.
And at the same time I'm doing what?(Praying)
That is why there is no room for enemy.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
But on your own case; ok now, I want to pray with my own help.
My own help. I want to pray on my own. Talk to me.
Don't disturb me , I am praying.
But if there is more important thing, I will stop my prayer, I will attend to him.
Like money, I trust you. Go and sit down sir. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Can you see the need to allow the Spirit of Father?
We don't know how to pray but the Spirit of Father helps us in our (what?) in our prayer.
But what is happening to you now? Take this:
The Spirit of Father in our heart enables us to pray naturally.
That word 'naturally' means it is not me - effortlessly
The Spirit of Father in our heart enables us to (do what) to pray naturally.
My heart, hear the voice of God.
My heart , hear the voice of Holy Spirit.
Let there be freedom . Let there be rest
In my heart. In my mind
And in my soul. In Jesus name.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest in my heart.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest
In my heart. In my mind..
And in my soul. In Jesus name.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest in my heart.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
My heart, hear the voice of the Lord.
Hallelujah!
My heart, hear the voice of God.
My heart , hear the voice of Holy Spirit.
My heart , hear the voice of God.
My heart , hear the voice of the Lord.
My heart , hear the voice of Holy Spirit.
My heart , hear the voice of God.
My heart , hear the voice of the Lord.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest
In my heart. In my mind..
And in my soul. In Jesus name.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest in my heart.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest
In my heart. In my mind..
And in my soul. In Jesus name.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest in my heart.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Oh We cry to you Jesus.
We don't know how to say
oh woooo oh woooo
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Oh We cry.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest in my heart.
In my heart . In my mind
And in my soul. In Jesus name.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest in my heart.
In my heart . In my mind
And in my soul. In Jesus name.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest in my heart.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest
In my heart, in my mind
And in my soul. In Jesus name.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest in my heart.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest.
In my heart, in my mind
And in my soul. In Jesus name.
Let there be freedom. Let there be rest in my heart.
Thank you
You will agree with me , that is the greatest achievement here on earth
to be able to know God's opinion about you, and about others.
and to get involved in God's projects
That is the greatest achievement.
I don't know any other achievement that can be compared to this.
THE GREATEST ACHIEVEMENT ON EARTH
I bless your heart. You may seated. Thank you.
Hallelujah!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So like I have said
Constantly pray in your heart, in hymns , in spiritual (what?) spiritual songs
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If it just the name Jesus. The name Jesus Christ, the blood of Jesus Christ.
You have done it all in your heart. That alone.
The name Jesus Christ, the blood of Jesus Christ.That alone in your heart
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Running and running over and over, that is...its more than enough.
To flash out all this strong conflict between flesh and spirit.
For, against, for, against, there is so much strong division
so much division in your heart
whether to go or not. Whether to do it or not. Whether to listen or not. Whether to pray or not
Flash this
Take a stand - your heart must take a stand for Jesus.Hallelujah!
Constantly pray in your heart in hymns, in spiritual songs making melodies in your heart for the Lord.
And constantly pray; In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus. You have said it all.
Then you can now tune to praises and worship in your heart
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I know you can save me. Save me Lord.
I know you can deliver me. Deliver me Lord. That's all.
Oh Lord Jesus, I know You can save me; Save me Lord!
I know You can deliver me. Deliver me Lord!
I know You can heal me; Heal me Lord !
With this, you will receive self - healing, self- deliverance
On your own you will be delivered without anybody delivering you.
On your own you get saved without anybody praying for you for salvation.
You get blessed abundantly without someone coming to pray for you
I repeat again
Lord Jesus, I know You can save me; save me Lord!
We that constantly running in your heart, you will soon get self deliverance, self salvation.
That is the salvation that no one come to pray for you; you pray for yourself.
Your heart will be clear. Like I have said
To be pure in heart is by ( what?) by meditation.
The Word becomes part of you.
Stand up sir, the Word, the Word of God becomes part of you
To be part of you is integral - like your hand.
Like this hand. This hand now, it's not only part -it is an integral.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You can not remove it. If anything happens to this hand; it happen to you all.
If you have a pain here; you have headache, everything is affected.
That is part; not only just part, an integral part. So
For the Word to become an integral part of you - meditation.
Our heart acts upon Word to give(what?) a new birth.
The Bible says God's power working through His Word and His Spirit give a new birth.
Let someone say;
God's power
When I say God's power, I mean Jesus.
Power -Jesus. Jesus - Power
God's power working through His Word and His Spirit give a new birth.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So Sit down sir. So thank you.
TT Monica Asefa 10/11/18